loginbd.com 2012-10-31

# LoginBD.Com- Specialized Commercial Search Engine for Bangladesh

**Overview**  
This is the Privacy Policy governing your use of the **LoginBD** (www.loginbd.com) Site. By using this Site, you consent to our Privacy Policy set out below. All terms not defined in this document have the meanings ascribed to them in the **Terms of Service Agreement** between you and **LoginBD** which by use of this Site you agree to accept. This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information and Anonymous Information you submit to us through our Site. This Privacy Policy applies only to Users; it does not apply to any information about companies or organizations that use the Services on the Site.

#### THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

**Registration Information**  
At the time you register to become a Registered User of the Site, you will be asked to complete a registration form which requires you to provide information such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as information about your business ("Registration Information.").

**Publishing Information**  
If you submit any information to **LoginBD** to be published on the Site through the publishing tools, including but not limited to Company Profile, Product Catalog, Trade Leads, Profile and any discussion forum, then you are deemed to have given consent to the publication of such information.

**Payment Information**  
If you establish a credit account with us or our providers or if you purchase a product or service from **LoginBD** or a vendor available through **LoginBD** ,we may collect additional information, including billing information, credit card numbers and expiration dates and tracking information from personal cheques or money orders.

**Statistical Information**  
In addition, we gather aggregate statistical information about our Site and Users, such as IP addresses, browser software, operating system, pages viewed, and number of sessions, unique visitors and so forth. 

### HOW WE USE AND DISCLOSE INFORMATION

**Registration Information**  
We use Personal Information for our own internal purposes including contacting you via email to inform you about updates to our Services and providing you with information relating to e-commerce transactions that you conduct on the Site. We reserve the right to disclose your information as required by law. We do not rent or sell our Users' Personal Information to third parties. We do, however, provide you with the opportunity to receive newsletters via email. If you decide to opt in to receive newsletters, you may opt out of receiving these newsletters at any time by clicking on your Preferences and choosing Email Notifications to Unsubscribe.

**Advertising**  
We may send you email communications including information that we think may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving these email communications either when you register to become a Member or via the Preferences section of your area. We do not send any of your Personal Information to our advertisers. You may see a cookie from a third-party banner server, and this cookie comes from the third party banner server, not LoginBD. Again, we do not pass along any Personal Information to this party.

**Legal Requests**  
**LoginBD** cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud, theft, harassment and other rights. We can and you authorize us to disclose any information about you, including the content of your online communications, if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us; (b) protect or defend the rights or property of LoginBD or third parties; (c) assist in an investigation; or (d) respond to an emergency that poses a threat to the safety of Users or other persons. 

**Comments Submitted by Users**  
LoginBD constantly seeks to improve the quality of the services we provide and the User experience on the Site. We value your input and encourage you to help us expand and make improvements to the Site by providing us with any thoughts or comments you might have regarding our services or the operation of the Site. 

**Security**  
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. We restrict access to user’s personal identifying information to employees except who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. 

**Editing / Updating Your Information**  
This Site gives the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  1. You may update your registration information using the Preferences page, under **LoginBD** site, in the **LoginBD** navigation bar after you register.  

  2. You may update your payment/credit card information using the Account page, under the **LoginBD** site section of the Site. 

  3. This Site Users have the opportunity to opt out of receiving promotional email communications from us, **LoginBD** newsletters and other Site information using Preferences, Email Notifications under the **LoginBD** site. 

**SAFETY MEASURES**  
We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information.  
As a Registered User, your Registration Information, Publishing Information and Payment Information (if any) can be viewed and edited through your Account which is protected by Password. We recommend that you do not divulge your Password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., User ID and Password) on the computer. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session.

**NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**  
We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time as our Services change and expand. If we make substantial changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post the updated policy on this page and we will post notice that this Privacy Policy has changed in the area of the Site and in this policy. The notification of revised terms will appear on the website 30 days prior to the changes taking place. Once any changes that we make to this Privacy Policy become effective, your continued use of the Site after such time will signify your acceptance of the new terms.
